[Social Media  
Management](https://www.mavrck.co/)

* Solutions
    
    Social Media Tools

    Later Social Users

    New Later Social Feature
    
    * [AI Caption WriterWrite Instagram captions faster (opens a new tab)](https://youtu.be/qFzHKuBmLkE)

* Product
    
    Social Platforms

        Instagram submenu

    Intro to Later Social
    
    * [New to Later? Watch this video!Later makes social media easy (opens a new tab)](https://youtu.be/GgzVSOKTb5g)

* Resources
    
    Marketing Training

    How to Use Later
    
    * [Get Later CertifiedBecome a Later pro for free (opens a new tab)](https://education.later.com/?utm_source=later.com&utm_medium=referral&utm_content=nav)
    
    Later Digital Events
    
    * [Later Presents: Social Media & Mental HealthCreate consistent content while prioritizing your mental health](https://later.com/resources/webinar/social-media-mental-health/)

Privacy Policies

Menu

Menu

Copied URL to clipboard!

Privacy Policy
==============

Sections

Later  / Victory Square Media
-----------------------------

Effective date: January 17, 2024

* * *

Victory Square Media Inc. ("us", "we", or "our") operates the https://later.com website as well as http://www.later.com website, http://www.latergram.me website, http://www.lat.gr website, http://app.later.com website, http://www.linkin.bio website, http://www.submit.media and the Later mobile application (the "Social Media Management Solution"). 

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Social Media Management Solution and the choices you have associated with that data. For clarity, these policies do not apply to your use of Later’s Influencer Marketing Solution by Mavrck including the [https://mavrck.co](https://mavrck.co/) website, Mavrck LLC (“Mavrck”)’s proprietary influencer marketing platform, or other influencer marketing and promotional services (the “Influencer Marketing Solution”). The Influencer Marketing Solution is owned and operated by Mavrck LLC and is subject to the Influencer Marketing Solution Privacy Policy. 

We use your data to provide and improve the Social Media Management Solution. By using the Social Media Management Solution, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions.

### Definitions

#### **Personal Data**

Personal Data means data about an individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).

#### **Usage Data**

Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Social Media Management Solution or from the Social Media Management Solution infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

#### **Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of data stored on a User’s device.

#### **Data Controller**

Data Controller means a person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data are, or are to be, processed.

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your data.

#### Data Processor (or Social Media Management Solution Providers)

Data Processor (or Social Media Management Solution Provider) means any person (other than an employee of the Data Controller) who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.

We may use the services of various Social Media Management Solution Providers in order to process your data more effectively.

#### **Data Subject**

Data Subject is any individual who is the subject of Personal Data.

#### **User**

The User is the individual using our Social Media Management Solution. The User corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.

### Information Collection And Use

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Social Media Management Solution to you.

#### Types of Data Collected

##### Personal Data

While using our Social Media Management Solution, we may ask you to provide us with Personal Data including:

* Email address
    
* First name and last name
    
* Social Network Authentication

We may also collect certain information automatically through cookies and similar tools (see Usage Data and Tracking & Cookies below.

We use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.

##### Usage Data

We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Social Media Management Solution or when you access the Social Media Management Solution by or through a mobile device ("Usage Data").

This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Social Media Management Solution that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

When you access the Social Media Management Solution by or through a mobile device, this Usage Data may include information such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

##### Tracking & Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Social Media Management Solution and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amounts of data which may include a unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Social Media Management Solution.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Social Media Management Solution.

Examples of Cookies we use:

* **Session Cookies.**We use Session Cookies to operate our Social Media Management Solution.
    
* **Preference Cookies.**We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
    
* **Security Cookies.**We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

Some of our service providers also use cookies and tracking tools. See Analytics and Behavioural Remarketing below.

### Use of Data

Victory Square Media Inc. uses the collected data:

* To provide and maintain our Social Media Management Solution
    
* To notify you about changes to our Social Media Management Solution
    
* To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Social Media Management Solution when you choose to do so
    
* To provide customer support
    
* To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Social Media Management Solution
    
* To monitor the usage of our Social Media Management Solution
    
* To train machine learning models
    
* To detect, prevent and address technical issues
    
* To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information

### Retention of Data

Victory Square Media Inc. will retain your Personal Data on our servers or those of our service providers only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

Victory Square Media Inc. will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Social Media Management Solution, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

### Transfer of Data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computer systems owned or controlled by us or our service providers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside Canada and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to Canada and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Victory Square Media Inc. will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

### Disclosure Of Data

#### Business Transaction

If Victory Square Media Inc. is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

#### Disclosure for Law Enforcement

Under certain circumstances, Victory Square Media Inc. may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

#### Legal Requirements

Victory Square Media Inc. may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

* To comply with a legal obligation
    
* To protect and defend the rights or property of Victory Square Media Inc.
    
* To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Social Media Management Solution
    
* To protect the personal safety of users of the Social Media Management Solution or the public
    
* To protect against legal liability

### Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

#### Analytics

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

##### Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Social Media Management Solution. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

##### Firebase

Firebase is an analytics service provided by Google Inc.

You may opt-out of certain Firebase features through your mobile device settings, such as your device advertising settings or by following the instructions provided by Google in their Privacy Policy: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

We also encourage you to review the Google's policy for safeguarding your data: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

##### Mixpanel

Mixpanel is provided by Mixpanel Inc

You can prevent Mixpanel from using your information for analytics purposes by opting-out. To opt-out of Mixpanel service, please visit this page:[https://mixpanel.com/optout/](https://mixpanel.com/optout/)

For more information on what type of information Mixpanel collects, please visit the Terms of Use page of Mixpanel:[https://mixpanel.com/terms/](https://mixpanel.com/terms/)

#### Behavioral Remarketing

Victory Square Media Inc. uses remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to you after you visited our Social Media Management Solution. We and our third-party vendors use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Social Media Management Solution.

##### Google AdWords

Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: [http://www.google.com/settings/ads](http://www.google.com/settings/ads)

Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on -[https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)\- for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

##### Twitter

Twitter remarketing service is provided by Twitter Inc.

You can opt-out from Twitter's interest-based ads by following their instructions: [https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170405](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170405)

You can learn more about the privacy practices and policies of Twitter by visiting their Privacy Policy page: [https://twitter.com/privacy](https://twitter.com/privacy)

##### Facebook

Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc.

You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: [https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950](https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950)To opt-out from Facebook's interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook: [https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217)

Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) Canada  
[http://youradchoices.ca/](http://youradchoices.ca/) or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook's Data Policy: [https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)

##### Pinterest

Pinterest remarketing service is provided by Pinterest Inc.  
You can opt-out from Pinterest's interest-based ads by enabling the "Do Not Track" functionality of your web browser or by following Pinterest instructions:[http://help.pinterest.com/en/articles/personalization-and-data](http://help.pinterest.com/en/articles/personalization-and-data)You can learn more about the privacy practices and policies of Pinterest by visiting their Privacy Policy page:[https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy](https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy)

#### Payments

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Social Media Management Solution. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

The payment processors we work with are:

##### Apple

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at: [https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/apple-pay/](https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/apple-pay/)

##### Stripe

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at: [https://stripe.com/us/privacy](https://stripe.com/us/privacy)

##### Profitwell

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at: [https://www.profitwell.com/privacy-policy](https://www.profitwell.com/privacy-policy)

##### YouTube API

Linking your YouTube account to the Social Media Management Solution involves using YouTube’s API connection. You can revoke the Social Media Management Solution’s access to this data through the Google security settings page, here: [https://myaccount.google.com/connections?filters=3,4&hl=en](https://myaccount.google.com/connections?filters=3,4&hl=en).

#### Legal Basis for Processing

We rely on one or more of the following legal grounds (as appropriate) to process Personal Data:

* To enter and perform a contract with you or to perform any steps you require from us before entering into a contract.
    
* To pursue our legitimate business interests in establishing, managing or concluding our business relationship with you.
    
* Where you have specifically consented to us processing your Personal Data.
    
* To comply with our legal obligations and establish, exercise or defend our legal rights.

Where Personal Data is processed with consent, you may (subject to contractual and legal restrictions) refuse to provide your consent, or choose to withdraw your consent by contacting us as described below. Note that if you refuse to consent, or withdraw your consent, to certain processing of your personal information, we may not be able to provide certain of our services.

### Security Of Data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Authorized employees, representatives and agents will have access to your Personal Data for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

### Your Rights

Victory Square Media Inc. aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

Whenever made possible, you can update your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to change your Personal Data, please contact us to make the required changes.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the right:

* To access and receive a copy of the Personal Data we hold about you
    
* To rectify any Personal Data held about you that is inaccurate
    
* To request the deletion of Personal Data held about you

You have the right to data portability for the information you provide to Victory Square Media Inc.. You can request to obtain a copy of your Personal Data in a commonly used electronic format so that you can manage and move it.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

### Links To Other Sites

Our Social Media Management Solution may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

### Children's Privacy

Our Social Media Management Solution does not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children have provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

### Security Vulnerabilities

If you wish to report a security vulnerability, please contact us with:

* Sufficient details of the vulnerability to allow it to be understood and reproduced.
    
* HTTP requests and responses, HTML snippets, screenshots or any other supporting evidence with personal data removed
    
* Proof of concept code (if available).
    
* The impact of the vulnerability.
    
* Any references or further reading that may be appropriate.

By email to:

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Social Media Management Solution, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

By email: [hello@later.com](mailto:hello@later.com)

Sections

**Later Influence Influencer Marketing Solution Privacy Policy**
----------------------------------------------------------------

Effective date: June 25, 2024

* * *

### **Overview**

Later’s Influencer Marketing Solution is powered by Mavrck LLC (formerly called “Mavrck” and now referred to as “**Later Influence**”, “**we**” “**us**” and/or “**our**”). Later Influence is a part of the Later Group of Companies and owns and operates proprietary web-based influencer marketing platform available at app.mavrck.co (the “**Influencer Marketing Platform**”), and makes available other associated marketing and promotional services, including through various “community” websites affiliated with Brands (as defined below) (collectively, the Web Sites, Influencer Marketing Platform, and such services, including any future features and applications, the “**Later Influence** **Services**”). The Later Influence Services are designed to offer users of the Later Influence Services (collectively, “**Users**,” “**you**,” or “**your**”) the opportunity to connect with each other and the third parties to which Later Influence provides marketing and promotional services (“**Brands**”), share information about and opinions on products and services offered by our Brands, and participate in certain sweepstakes, contests, challenges and other promotions (“**Promotions**”).

For clarity, this Privacy Policy does not apply to your use of Later’s Social Media Management Solution (also referred to as Later Social), including your use of the following Later websites, products and services” [http://www.later.com](http://www.later.com/) website, [http://www.latergram.me](http://www.latergram.me/) website, [http://www.lat.gr](http://www.lat.gr/) website, [http://www.linkin.bio](http://www.linkin.bio/) website, [https://app.later.com](https://app.later.com/), [http://www.submit.media](http://www.submit.media/) email, the Later Community (the “Community”) and the Later mobile application (the “**Social Media Management Solution**”). The Social Media Management Solution is owned and operated by Victory Square Media Inc. and subject to a separate Victory Square Media Inc. privacy policy.

This Privacy Policy sets forth Later Influence’s policy with respect to information that, alone or in combination with other information, could be used to identify you (“**Personal Data**”) and other information that is collected from Users. **This Privacy Policy explains what Personal Data we collect through the Later Influence Services, how we use and share that data, and your choices concerning our data practices.** This Privacy Policy forms part of our Influencer Terms of Use for Influencer Marketing Solution, which are available at: https://later.com/terms/.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to Personal Data that our Brands provide to us or otherwise make available to the Later Influence Services, that we process on our Brands’ behalf. Our practices concerning this data are addressed in our contract with the applicable Brand. 

By using the Later Influence Services you acknowledge and agree to the practices and policies disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

### **1\. Information We Collect**

When you interact with us through the Later Influence Services, we may collect Personal Data and other information from you, as described below:

Customer Account and Inquiries: If you are a Brand or prospective customer, we collect and process your Personal Data when you (i) visit the Influencer Marketing Platform, sign up for a Later Influence webcast or other event or make a request to receive information about Later Influence or the Later Influence Services, including to book a demo, (ii) contact Later Influence’s sales team or customer support team, and (iii) sign up for a Later Influence account and use the Later Influence Services. The Personal Data we collect may include your first and last name, job title, company name, email address, mailing address, payment and billing information, phone number, country location.

Personal Data That You Provide Through the Later Influence Services: We collect Personal Data from you when you voluntarily provide such information in connection with your use of the Later Influence Services, such as when you contact us with inquiries, respond to one of our surveys, register for access to the Later Influence Services or use certain Later Influence Services, including when done so through their integration into social media services, such as Facebook and Twitter (“Social Media Services”) (for more information on the information we may receive from Social Media Services, please see the “Personal Data From Social Media Services” section below).  Data collected may include: First Name, Last Name, Profile Photo, Email, Birthday, Gender, Location, Hometown, Current City, Current State, Current Country, Brands you mention, IP Address, Topics/Keywords you use, and your social post performance.

Personal Data From Social Media Services: When you provide Later Influence access to your Social Media Services account, we will collect relevant information necessary to enable the Later Influence Services to access that Social Media Service, however you will provide your login information, like your password, directly to such Social Media Service (and not to Later Influence).

As part of the integration of the Later Influence Services with your Social Media Services account, the Social Media Service will provide Later Influence with access to certain information that you have provided to such Social Media Service, including but not limited to post-related meta data from your Facebook wall (e.g., post type, date of creation, date of update, post creator, permanent link, and the number of “Likes” and “Comments”). To access your Social Media Services account, we provide a link that directs you to a Social Media Service, like Facebook, where you may access the Later Influence Services directly. We will use, store and disclose such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and, if and to the extent applicable, the policies of such Social Media Services. However, please remember that the manner in which Social Media Services use, store and disclose your information is governed by the policies of the applicable Social Media Services provider, and, as a result, Later Influence shall not have any liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of Social Media Services that may be enabled within and/or otherwise accessible through the Later Influence Services.

Personal Data Obtained from Other Sources: We may collect information about you from publicly accessible sources in compliance with applicable laws. For example, we may collect information that you have made publicly available online or that we obtain from other public sources, including Social Media Services (please refer to the “Personal Data From Social Media Services” section above) and third-party influencer databases and platforms.

Personal Data Collected on Behalf of Brands: When using the Later Influence Services, you may choose to enter into a relationship directly with Brands by applying for campaigns offered by those Brands. We collect under the direction of our Brands information about influencers with whom Brands engage on Social Media Services. If you are a User of one of our Brands and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Brands that use the Later Influence Services or you would like to access, correct or request deletion of your data, please contact the Brand that you interact with directly.

Passively Collected Data: When you interact with the Later Influence Services, we and third parties that provide functionality on the Later Influence Services, may passively collect and store certain types of information through automatic data collection tools including cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, embedded web links and similar technology.  Such information may include but is not limited to information about your device, referring/exit pages and URLs and number of clicks. Please see the “Cookies” section below to learn more about how we use cookies and other similar technologies. Later Influence may store such information itself or such information may be included in databases owned and maintained by Brands, agents or service providers including, but not limited to, Amazon Web Services Inc., Netra, Indico.io, Front, Endpoint Direct, and Zendesk. The Later Influence Services may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of Users, the number of visitors to each page of our Web Sites, and the domain names of our Users’ internet service providers.

### **2\. Our Use of Your Personal Data**

Later Influence uses the Personal Data you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.  In particular, Later Influence uses your Personal Data for the following purposes:

To provide Brands and Users with access to the Later Influence Services.  This processing is necessary to perform our contract with our Brands.

As necessary for certain legitimate business interests, which include the following:

* To respond to our Brands’ or Users’ inquiries, fulfill requests for products and services, respond to comments, feedback or questions;
    
* To pursue the interest of our Brands in engaging with Users when they are interacting with the relevant Brand;
    
* To pursue the interest of our Users in connecting with each other and with Brands;
    
* To personalize the content you see. For example, we use information about your use of the Later Influence Services, including information that we obtain through cookies and other technologies, to better understand your needs and interests in order to personalize your experience by presenting on the Later Influence Services products and services tailored to your interests;
    
* To send administrative information to you, for example, information regarding the Later Influence Services, and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies;
    
* To analyze usage of the Later Influence Services and provide, maintain and improve the content and functionality of the Later Influence Services. For example, we regularly fix bugs or User experience issues that may be tied to particular User accounts. We use cookies to analyze how Users interact with the Later Influence Services. And that analysis can help us improve the Later Influence Services;
    
* If you ask us to delete your data and we are required to fulfill your request, to keep basic data to identify you and prevent further unwanted processing;
    
* To prevent fraud, criminal activity, or misuses of the Later Influence Services and to ensure the security of our IT systems, architecture and networks;
    
* To comply with legal obligations and legal process and to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or other third parties.

Marketing. We or our affiliates may contact you to tell you about services or products we believe will be of interest to you. If we do, where required by law, for example laws in the EU, we will only send you marketing information if you consent to us doing so at the time you provide us with your Personal Data. You may opt-out of receiving such emails by following the instructions contained in each promotional email we send you. In addition, if at any time you do not wish to receive future marketing communications, please contact us (refer to the “Contact Us” section below). If you unsubscribe from our marketing list, we will continue to contact you via email regarding the provision of the Later Influence Services and to respond to your requests.

### **3\. Our Disclosure of Your Personal Data.**

We consider your Personal Data to be a vital part of our relationship with you. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Data with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:

Business Transfers: As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale of all or a portion of our assets, transition of service to another provider, merger, reorganization, financing due diligence, bankruptcy, receivership, dissolution or similar event, Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets. For added certainty, we may also share your Personal Data internally with our affiliates for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

Brands: Many of the Later Influence Services are offered in connection with a specific Brand.  Later Influence shares the information you provide, including Personal Data, with Brands who provide you content targeted to your interests (including opportunities to participate in community forums and other interactive experiences), in accordance with the following: (i) with your informed consent (when we or our Brands have a direct interaction with you), or (ii) when we do not obtain your Personal Data directly from you (as described above), as necessary for our, our Brands’ and/or our Users’ legitimate interests (described above) and as permitted by applicable law (you may object at any time to such sharing, as described below). A Brand may use and disclose the Personal Data it receives from Later Influence Services according to the Brand’s individual privacy policies.

Agents, Service Providers: Later Influence, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions and to help us understand and improve the use of our Services. Such parties providers of database storage and management services, customer support services, email management solutions, Later Influence Services hosting and other information technology providers, processing payments, providers of website analytics and direct marketing campaigns services, providers of artificial intelligence-based and machine learning solutions (such as providers of visual intelligence and visual search applications for pictures and videos). We may share your Personal Data with vendors and service providers retained in connection with providing the Later Influence Services on our behalf and under our instructions. For Personal Data transferred to us from the UK, EU or EEA member countries and Switzerland in accordance with the EU-U.S. DPF, the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF or the Swiss-U.S. DPF, we will remain liable under the Data Privacy Framework if third-party agents or service providers that we engage to process the personal information on our behalf do so in a manner inconsistent with the Data Privacy Framework (Please see further the “Data Privacy Framework” section below.)

Legal Requirements: Later Influence may disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law, in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements, or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of Later Influence or our Brands, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of Users or the public, (iv) protect against legal liability or suspected fraud, or (v) investigate, prevent, or take action regarding violations of Later Influence’s Terms of Use.

For information on your choices and means for limiting use and disclosure of your Personal Data, please see the “Users’ Rights” section below.

### **4\. Account Deactivation and Deletion**

If you no longer desire to use the Later Influence Services, you may deactivate or delete your account by sending an email to support@mavrck.co. Note that de-activating your account with Later Influence may not fully remove the data collected from Facebook and other Social Media Services, or the data held or collected by Brands.

### **5\. Data Retention**

We will keep your Personal Data for as long as reasonably necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, while we have a legitimate business need to do so, or as required by law (e.g. for tax, legal, accounting or other purposes), whichever is longer.

If you have elected to receive marketing communications from us, we retain information about your marketing preferences until you opt out of receiving these communications and in accordance with our policies.

To determine the appropriate retention period for your Personal Data, we will consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the Personal Data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of your Personal Data, the purposes for which we use your Personal Data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.

### **6\. Exclusions**

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information collected by Later Influence other than Personal Data collected through the Later Influence Services.

Notice for Residents of the United States: If you are a resident of the United States, please note that, this Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to Later Influence through the Later Influence Services or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, questions, comments, suggestions, ideas, feedback or other information provided by a User to Later Influence or posted by a User to any public areas of the Later Influence Services, including those integrated with or into Social Media Services (e.g., bulletin boards, community web sites, or your Facebook wall); any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products; and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and Later Influence shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information for any purpose, commercial or otherwise, to others without limitation or attribution.

### **7\. EU, Switzerland, and UK Visitors**

**Scope.** This section applies if you are visitor to or User of the Later Influence Services in the EU (for these purposes, reference to the EU also includes the European Economic Area countries of Iceland, Liechtenstein and Norway and, to the extent applicable, Switzerland) or the United Kingdom.

**Data Controller.** Later Influence is the data controller for processing Personal Data that we collect from or about you through the Influencer Marketing Platform, but we act as a data processor for Personal Data provided or otherwise made available to us by Brands through the Later Influence Services, which we process on Brands’ behalf pursuant to our contract with the applicable Brand. To find the contact information of our representative in the EU for purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation, please see the “Contact Us” section below.

**Your Rights.** Subject to applicable EU law, you have the following rights in relation to your Personal Data:

* Right of access: If you ask us, we will confirm whether we are processing your Personal Data and, if so, provide you with a copy of that Personal Data along with certain other details. If you require additional copies, we may need to charge a reasonable fee.
    
* Right to rectification: If your Personal Data is inaccurate or incomplete, you are entitled to ask that we correct or complete it. If we shared your Personal Data with others, we will tell them about the correction where possible. If you ask us, and where possible and lawful to do so, we will also tell you with whom we shared your Personal Data so you can contact them directly.
    
* Right to erasure: You may ask us to delete or remove your Personal Data, such as where you withdraw your consent. If we shared your data with others, we will tell them about the erasure where possible. If you ask us, and where possible and lawful to do so, we will also tell you with whom we shared your Personal Data with so you can contact them directly.
    
* Right to restrict processing: You may ask us to restrict or ‘block’ the processing of your Personal Data in certain circumstances, such as where you contest the accuracy of the data or object to us processing it (please read below for information on your right to object). We will tell you before we lift any restriction on processing. If we shared your Personal Data with others, we will tell them about the restriction where possible. If you ask us, and where possible and lawful to do so, we will also tell you with whom we shared your Personal Data so you can contact them directly.
    
* Right to data portability: You have the right to obtain your Personal Data from us that you consented to give us or that was provided to us as necessary in connection with our contract with you, and that is processed by automated means. We will give you your Personal Data in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format. You may reuse it elsewhere.
    
* Right to object: You may ask us at any time to stop processing your Personal Data, and we will do so:
    
* If we are relying on a legitimate interest to process your Personal Data (refer to the “Our Use of Your Personal Data” section above) — unless we demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing or
    
* If we are processing your Personal Data for direct marketing.
    
* Right to withdraw consent: If we rely on your consent to process your Personal Data, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. Withdrawal of consent will not affect any processing of your data before we received notice that you wished to withdraw consent.
    
* Right to lodge a complaint with the data protection authority: If you have a concern about our privacy practices, including the way we handled your Personal Data, you can report it to the data protection authority that is authorized to hear those concerns.

Please see the “Contact Us” section below for information on how to exercise your rights.

**Legitimate Interest.** “Legitimate interests” means our interests in conducting our business, managing and delivering the best services to you. It also refers to our Brands’ and Users’ interest in creating engagement with Brands and each other. This Privacy Policy describes when we process your Personal Data for such legitimate interests, what these interests are and your rights. We will not use your Personal Data for activities where the impact on you overrides our interests, unless we have your consent or those activities are otherwise required or permitted by law.

### **8\. Children**

Later Influence does not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any Personal Data through the Later Influence Services. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Data through the Later Influence Services without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Data to Later Influence through the Later Influence Services, please contact us, and we will delete that information from our databases.

### **9\. Links to Other Web Sites**

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Later Influence Services. The Later Influence Services may contain links to other web sites or provide you the opportunity to post to third party sites not operated or controlled by Later Influence (the “External Sites”). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the External Sites. The links from the Later Influence Services do not imply that Later Influence endorses or has reviewed the External Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies.

### **10\. Social Media**

Through the Later Influence Services, you may choose to access certain Social Media Services. When you elect to access and use the Social Media Services, you will be sharing your information (which will include Personal Data) with those Social Media Services. As with other External Sites, the information that you share with the Social Media Services will be governed by the privacy policies and terms of service of the providers of such Social Media Services and not by the Later Influence’s policies and procedures. You may also be able to modify your privacy settings with these Social Media Services to, for example, control what information the Social Media Services disclose to other entities, including Later Influence.

### 11\. Cookies

We use cookies and other technologies to operate and administer the Later Influence Services, make it easier for you to use the Later Influence Services during future visits, and gather usage data on the Later Influence Services.

What Are Cookies. A “cookie” is a piece of information sent to your browser by a website you visit. By choosing to use the Later Influence Services after having been notified of our use of cookies in the ways described in this Privacy Policy, and, in applicable jurisdictions, through notice and unambiguous acknowledgement of your consent, you agree to such use.

Some cookies expire after a certain amount of time, or upon logging out (session cookies), others remain on your computer or terminal device for a longer period (persistent cookies). The Later Influence Services use first party cookies (cookies set directly by Later Influence) as well as third party cookies, as described below. For more details on cookies please visit All About Cookies.

Type of Cookies Used. The Later Influence Services use the following technologies:

* Strictly Necessary Cookies: Used to provide you (notably, when you log in at app.mavrck.co) with the services available through the Later Influence Services and to use some of their features, such as the ability to log-in and access secure areas. These cookies are served by Later Influence and are essential for using and navigating the Later Influence Services. Without these cookies, basic functions of the Later Influence Services would not work. Because these cookies are strictly necessary to deliver the Later Influence Services, you cannot refuse them.
    
* Analytics/Performance Cookies: Used to recognize and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around the Later Influence Services when they are using them. This helps us improve the way the Later Influence Services work, for example, by making sure Users are finding what they need easily. The Later Influence Services use:
    
* Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). The information collected by Google (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. How long a Google Analytics cookie remains on your computer or device depends on what it is and what it is used for. Some Google Analytics cookies expire at the end of your browser session, whilst others can remain for up to two years. You can prevent your data from being collected by Google Analytics on the Later Influence Services by downloading and installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on for your current web browser. For more information on Google Analytics privacy practices, visit: https://policies.google.com/privacy.
    
* Snowplow, a web analytics service provided by Snowplow Analytics Limited. For more information on Snowplow’s privacy practices, visit: https://snowplow.io/privacy-policy/.
    
* Advertising Cookies: If you use, or request that we use on your behalf, trackable links, we use Everflow, a tool (provided by Everflow Technologies Inc.) that uses cookies to enable tracking clicks on our links. For more information on EverFlows’s privacy practices visit: https://www.everflow.io/legal/privacy-policy.

Other Technologies. From time to time we may provide our influencers and partners with pixel tags to get information about visitors’ usage of a website. Pixel tags are a technology similar to cookies that can be embedded in online content or within the body of an email for the purpose of tracking activity on websites (for example, to know when content has been shown to you), or to know when you have viewed particular contente. Please review the privacy or cookie policies or pop-ups provided on the applicable website you interact with to receive more information on the use of such technologies.

Your Choices. On most web browsers, you will find a “help” section on the toolbar. Please refer to this section for information on how to receive a notification when you are receiving a new cookie and how to turn cookies off. Please see the links below for guidance on how to modify your web browser’s settings on the most popular browsers:

* Internet Explorer
    
* Mozilla Firefox
    
* Google Chrome
    
* Apple Safari

Please note that if you limit the ability of websites to set cookies, you may be unable to access certain parts of the Later Influence Services and you may not be able to benefit from the full functionality of the Later Influence Services.

If you access the Later Influence Services on your mobile device, you may not be able to control tracking technologies through the settings.

We partner with third parties to display advertising on Later Influence Services or to manage our advertising on other sites, as described above. Our third-party partners may use cookies or similar tracking technologies to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising, visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s online resources, at http://www.networkadvertising.org and follow the opt-out instructions there or if located in the European Union, visit the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance’s Your Online Choices opt-out tool here.  Please note that you will continue to receive generic ads.

### **12\. Security**

You use Later Influence at your own risk. Later Influence takes reasonable and appropriate measures to protect the Personal Data provided via the Later Influence Services from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. These measures are regularly assessed and improved according to technological developments in the field. However, no Internet or email transmission is ever fully secure or error-free. In particular, email sent to or from the Later Influence Services may not be secure. Therefore, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any Personal Data to Later Influence via the Internet. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share information. Therefore, we cannot, and do not, guarantee that information or content posted by a User on or through the Later Influence Services will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Later Influence services or Social Media Services.

### **13\. Your California Privacy Rights**

In accordance with the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”), this section is intended to inform California residents of (1) the Personal Information that we collect and how we disclose that information, and (2) the privacy rights California residents may have relating to their Personal Information and how those rights can be exercised.

#### \[H4\] Personal Information Collection and Disclosure

The following disclosures are intended to provide additional information about (1) the categories of Personal Information we collect, and (2) how and to whom we disclose that Personal Information. Nothing in this section limits our ability to use or disclose information as described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy.

* Categories of Personal Information Collected: In the past 12 months, we have collected the categories of Personal Information, as described in greater detail in the “Information We Collect” section above.
    
* Identification Information, such as your name, email address, phone number, physical address or zip code, account information (e.g., password or other information that helps us confirm that it is you accessing your account), and Device Identifiers.
    
* Demographic Information, as well as information about your interests and preferences.
    
* Online Activity Information, such as the Device used to access a Service, your internet service provider (ISP), date and time of your visit, browser language, browser type, operating system referring and exit pages and URLs, amount of time spent on particular pages, which parts of our Services you use, which links you click, search terms, traffic and related statistics, the location of the Device, keywords, and/or other general browsing data or Usage Information.
    
* Commercial Information, such as purchase, payment (e.g., credit card or bank account information), and billing information if you choose to purchase products or services through the Services.
    
* Sources of Personal Information: We collect the above categories of Personal Information from you, our Partners, our analytics providers, vendors, service providers, and as otherwise described in the “Information We Collect” section above.
    
* Purposes of Collection and Disclosure: We collect and disclose the above categories of Personal Information for the business and commercial purposes described in the “Our Use Of Your Personal Data” and “Our Disclosure of Your Personal Data” sections above.
    
* Categories of Personal Information Disclosed for a Business Purpose: In the past 12 months, we have disclosed for a business purpose all of the above categories of Personal Information to service providers and as described in the “Our Disclosure of Your Personal Data” section above.
    
* Categories of Personal Information Sold: Later Influence does not make your Personal Information available for purchase or otherwise share your information in exchange for monetary compensation. Certain sharing of your information, however, may be considered a “sale” under the CCPA’s broad definition.  In particular, in the last 12 months, if you have visited our Sites, we may have shared your Identification Information, Demographic Information and Online Activity Information with advertising partners to match and serve our targeted advertisements on third party websites.  (You can find additional information about cookies in the “Cookies” section above.)  See below for information about how to opt out of the sharing of your Personal Information for these purposes.

#### California Privacy Rights

To the extent provided for by the CCPA and subject to applicable exceptions and exclusions, California residents have the following privacy rights in relation to the Personal Information we collect:

* The right to know what Personal Information we have collected and how we have used and disclosed that Personal Information.
    
* The right to request deletion of your Personal Information.
    
* The right to opt out of the sale of your Personal Information.
    
* The right to be free from discrimination for the exercise of your privacy rights.

Additionally, under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, California residents may have the right to request the categories of Personal Information we disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes in the year preceding the request, the names and addresses of such third parties, and, in certain circumstances, examples of the products or services marketed by such third parties.

Exercising Your Rights: California residents can exercise the above privacy rights by emailing us at privacy@mavrck.co.

Verification: In order to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access or deletion, we may require you to verify your credentials before you can submit a request to know or delete Personal Information. If you do not have an account with us, or if we suspect fraudulent or malicious activity, we may ask you to provide additional Personal Information for verification. If we cannot verify your identity, we will not provide or delete your Personal Information.

Authorized Agents: You may submit a request to know or a request to delete your Personal Information through an authorized agent. If you do so, we may require the agent to present signed written permission to act on your behalf and you may also be required to independently verify your identity with us and confirm that you have provided the agent permission to submit the request.

### **14\. Do Not Track Signals**

The Later Influence Services currently do not respond to “Do Not Track” (“DNT”) signals and operate as described in this Privacy Policy whether or not a DNT signal is received. If we do respond to DNT signals in the future, we will update this Privacy Policy to describe how we do so.

### **15\. Other Terms and Conditions**

Your access to and use of the Later Influence Services is subject to any additional terms applicable to such Later Influence Services that may be posted on the Later Influence Services from time to time, including without limitation, Later Influence’s Terms of Use available at [https://later.com/terms/](https://later.com/terms/) and additional terms and conditions set forth by our Brands, including those related to Promotions.

### **16\. Changes to Later Influence’s Privacy Policy**

The Later Influence Services and our business may change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be necessary for Later Influence to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Later Influence reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice. Later Influence strives to provide notifications to Users in a timely manner, but is not responsible for lost or late notifications. If the changes are significant, we will, in our sole discretion unless required by the law, post a notice on the homepage of our Web Sites or notify you at the email address we have on file for your account and provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of your continued use of our Services. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any Personal Data. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. Your continued use of the Later Influence Services after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy (or after we have notified you, if applicable) shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

### **17\. International Users**

If you are using the Later Influence Services from outside of the United States, you expressly acknowledge and agree that your Personal Data and other information will be processed in the United States and in other third countries. Privacy and data security laws may be  less stringent than or otherwise different from the laws in effect in your country of residence.  You expressly agree to the processing of your Personal Data and other information in accordance with this Policy. If you are using the Later Influence Services from the EU or the EEA, your Personal Data will be processed and transferred to the United States in accordance with the Data Privacy Framework Principles as explained below.

### **18\. EU-US Data Privacy Framework**

General: Later Influence complies with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF), the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce. Later Influence has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (EU-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from the European Union in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and from the United Kingdom (and Gibraltar) in reliance on the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF. Later Influence has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from Switzerland in reliance on the Swiss-U.S. DPF. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the EU-U.S. DPF Principles and/or the Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles, the Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Data Privacy Framework (DPF) program, and to view our certification, please visit [https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/).

Later Influence is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission and of other relevant US statutory bodies authorized to verify and ensure compliance with the Data Privacy Framework Principles.

Complaints: In compliance with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF), the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF), Later Influence commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information transferred to the U.S. pursuant to the EU-U.S. DPF, the UK extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. DPF. EU, UK, and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints should first contact Later Influence at privacy@mavrck.co. 

Later Influence has further committed to refer unresolved DPF Principles-related complaints to a U.S.-based independent dispute resolution mechanism, BBB NATIONAL PROGRAMS. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit www.bbbprograms.org/dpf-complaints for more information and to file a complaint. This service is provided free of charge to you.

If your DPF complaint cannot be resolved through the above channels, under certain conditions, you may invoke binding arbitration for some residual claims not resolved by other redress mechanisms. See https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/article/ANNEX-I-introduction-dpf 

Your Rights: You have the right to access the Personal Data in our possession that you have previously submitted via the Later Influence Services and to correct, change, update, or delete your Personal Data. You have also the right to object to the disclosure of your information to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, except for disclosures made to agents and service providers, as well as to the use of your information for a purpose that is materially different from the purposes for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by you. You may contact us as specified below to exercise these rights.

### 19\. Contact details

Please feel free to contact us if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the information practices of the Later Influence Services.

You may contact us at privacy@mavrck.co or by regular mail addressed to:

Mavrck LLC, a Delaware limited liability company

53 State Street  
21st Floor – Suite 2105  
Boston, MA 02109

General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) – European Representative

Pursuant to Article 27 of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), our company has appointed European Data Protection Office (EDPO) as its GDPR Representative in the EU. You can contact EDPO regarding matters pertaining to the GDPR:

* by using EDPO’s online request form: https://edpo.com/gdpr-data-request/
    
* by writing to EDPO at Avenue Huart Hamoir 71, 1030 Brussels, Belgium

Sections

**Later Influence Cookie Policy**
---------------------------------

Last updated: June 25, 2024

This Cookie Policy applies to citizens and legal permanent residents of the European Economic Area and Switzerland

### 1\. Introduction

Our website, [app.mavrck.co](https://app.mavrck.co/) (hereinafter: “the website") uses cookies and other related technologies. Note, for simplicity, all technologies are referred to as “cookies". Cookies are also placed by third parties we have engaged. In the document below we inform you about the use of cookies on our website. This Cookie Policy should be read in conjunction with our [Privacy Policy](https://www.mavrck.co/legal/privacypolicy/). If you have any questions or concerns about the Cookie Policy or its implementation, please contact us at 1-844-MAVRCK1 or as otherwise described in our [Privacy Policy](https://www.mavrck.co/legal/privacypolicy/).

### 2\. What are cookies?

A cookie is a small simple file that is sent along with pages of this website and stored by your browser on the hard drive of your computer or another device. The information stored therein may be returned to our servers or to the servers of the relevant third parties during a subsequent visit.

We use cookies — and other similar technologies, which we describe below — to collect information about your browsing activities and to distinguish you from other users of our services. Use of cookies will improve your experience when you use our services, and allow us to enhance the functionality, increase the security, and measure the use and effectiveness of our services.

### 3\. What are scripts?

A script is a piece of program code that is used to make our website function properly and interactively. This code is executed on our server or on your device.

### 4\. What is a web beacon?

A web beacon (or a pixel tag) is a small, invisible piece of text or image on a website that is used to monitor traffic on a website. In order to do this, various data about you is stored using web beacons.

### **5\. Cookies**

#### 5.1 Functional cookies

Some cookies ensure that certain parts of the website work properly and that your user preferences remain known. By placing functional cookies, we make it easier for you to visit our website. This way, you do not need to repeatedly enter the same information when navigating our website. These cookies also allow us to provide services, such as secure user login, remembering your account preferences, and other critical security features aimed at preventing fraud and debugging the service. Data collected through these cookies are processed within the scope of our legitimate interest in providing and operating our services.

#### 5.2 Statistics cookies

We use statistics cookies to optimize the website experience for our users. With these statistics cookies we get insights in the usage of our website. We ask for your consent via our Cookie Banner to place statistics cookies.

#### 5.3 Marketing/Tracking cookies

Marketing/Tracking cookies are cookies or any other form of local storage; used to create user profiles to display advertising or to track the user on this website or across several websites for similar marketing purposes. These cookies are also used to deliver advertisements that are more relevant to you and your interests when you are on other websites across the internet. The information collected by these cookies will be used to track visits and actions on our services, as well as to deliver reporting and analytics to us and our partners.

We also use advertising cookies, enabling us to gain insights into our advertising campaign results. We do this by creating a profile based on your behavior. With these cookies, you, as website visitor, are linked to a unique ID, but these cookies will not profile your behavior and interests to serve personalized ads.

In addition, we have included buttons for Facebook, LinkedIn, Instagram, and TikTok to promote our profiles or help you share our content on social networks like LinkedIn, Instagram, and TikTok. These buttons work using pieces of code from Facebook, LinkedIn, Instagram, and TikTok themselves. Such code relies on cookies or similar tracking technologies. These social media buttons can also store and process certain information so that a personalized advertisement can be shown to you.

Please read the privacy statement of these social networks (which can change regularly) to read what they do with your personal data that they process using these cookies. The data that is retrieved is anonymized as much as possible.

As these cookies are tracking cookies, we ask for your consent to place these via our Cookie Banner.

#### 5.4 Preferences cookies

These cookies allow us to remember information that changes the way that our website behaves or looks, like your preferred language.

### 6\. Placed Cookies

#### Wistia

##### Usage

We use Wistia for video display. [Read more](https://cookiedatabase.org/service/wistia/)

##### Sharing data

For more information, please read the [Wistia Privacy Statement](https://wistia.com/privacy).

| Marketing/Tracking |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [wistia](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/wistia/wistia/) | persistent | Store performed actions on the website |

#### Elementor

##### Usage

We use Elementor for content creation. [Read more](https://cookiedatabase.org/service/elementor/)

##### Sharing data

This data is not shared with third parties.

| Statistics (anonymous) |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [elementor](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/elementor/elementor/) | persistent | Store performed actions on the website |

#### HubSpot

##### Usage

We use HubSpot for marketing automation (automated email marketing). [Read more](https://cookiedatabase.org/service/hubspot/)

##### Sharing data

For more information, please read the [HubSpot Privacy Statement](https://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy).

| Purpose pending investigation |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [hs-messages-hide-welcome-message](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/hubspot/hs-messages-hide-welcome-message/) | 1 day |     |

| Functional |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [\_\_hs\_opt\_out](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/hubspot/__hs_opt_out/) | 6 months | Store cookie consent preferences |
| [\_\_hssc](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/hubspot/__hssc/) | 30 minutes | Store anonymized statistics |
| [hs\_ab\_test](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/hubspot/hs_ab_test/) | session | Store ID’s of experiments and sessions for A/B testing |
| [\_\_hs\_do\_not\_track](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/hubspot/__hs_do_not_track/) | 6 months | Store ‘do not track’ signals |

| Preferences |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [messagesUtk](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/hubspot/messagesutk/) | 13 months | Store browser details |
| [hs-messages-is-open](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/hubspot/hs-messages-is-open/) | 30 minutes | Store anonymized statistics |

| Marketing/Tracking |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [\_\_hstc](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/hubspot/__hstc/) | 13 months | Store time of visit |

#### WooCommerce

##### Usage

We use WooCommerce for webshop management. [Read more](https://cookiedatabase.org/service/woocommerce/)

##### Sharing data

This data is not shared with third parties.

| Statistics |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [History.store](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/woocommerce/history-store/) |     | Store last visit |

#### Pinterest

##### Usage

We use Pinterest for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons. [Read more](https://cookiedatabase.org/service/pinterest/)

##### Sharing data

For more information, please read the [Pinterest Privacy Statement](https://policy.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy).

| Marketing/Tracking |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [\_pin\_unauth](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/pinterest/_pin_unauth/) | 1 day |     |

#### Hotjar

##### Usage

We use Hotjar for heat maps and screen recordings. [Read more](https://cookiedatabase.org/service/hotjar/)

##### Sharing data

For more information, please read the [Hotjar Privacy Statement](https://help.hotjar.com/hc/en-us/articles/6952777582999-Cookies-Set-by-the-Hotjar-Tracking-Code).

| Statistics |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [\_hjSessionUser\_\*](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/hotjar/_hjsessionuser_/) | 1 year | Store a unique user ID |

#### Google Analytics

##### Usage

We use Google Analytics for website statistics. [Read more](https://cookiedatabase.org/service/google-analytics/)

##### Sharing data

For more information, please read the [Google Analytics Privacy Statement](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

| Statistics |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [\_ga](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/google-analytics/_ga/) | 2 years | Store and count pageviews |

#### Stripe

##### Usage

We use Stripe for payment processing. [Read more](https://cookiedatabase.org/service/stripe/)

##### Sharing data

For more information, please read the [Stripe Privacy Statement](https://stripe.com/privacy/).

| Functional |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [\_\_stripe\_mid](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/stripe/__stripe_mid/) | 1 year | Provide fraud prevention |

#### WPML

##### Usage

We use WPML for locale management. [Read more](https://cookiedatabase.org/service/wpml/)

##### Sharing data

This data is not shared with third parties.

| Functional |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [wp-wpml\_current\_language](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/wpml/wp-wpml_current_language/) | 1 day | Store language settings |

#### Google Fonts

##### Usage

We use Google Fonts for display of webfonts. [Read more](https://cookiedatabase.org/service/google-fonts/)

##### Sharing data

For more information, please read the [Google Fonts Privacy Statement](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

| Marketing/Tracking |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [Google Fonts API](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/google-fonts/tcb_google_fonts/) | expires immediately | Read user IP address |

#### Google reCAPTCHA

##### Usage

We use Google reCAPTCHA for spam prevention. [Read more](https://cookiedatabase.org/service/google-recaptcha/)

##### Sharing data

For more information, please read the [Google reCAPTCHA Privacy Statement](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

| Marketing/Tracking |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [rc::c](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/google-recaptcha/rcc/) | session | Read and filter requests from bots |
| [rc::b](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/google-recaptcha/rcb/) | session | Read and filter requests from bots |
| [rc::a](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/google-recaptcha/rca/) | persistent | Read and filter requests from bots |

#### Google Maps

##### Usage

We use Google Maps for maps display. [Read more](https://cookiedatabase.org/service/google-maps/)

##### Sharing data

For more information, please read the [Google Maps Privacy Statement](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

| Marketing/Tracking |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [Google Maps API](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/google-maps/google-maps-api/) | expires immediately | Read user IP address |

#### YouTube

##### Usage

We use YouTube for video display. [Read more](https://cookiedatabase.org/service/youtube/)

##### Sharing data

For more information, please read the [YouTube Privacy Statement](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

| Marketing/Tracking |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [GPS](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/youtube/gps/) | session | Store location data |
| [YSC](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/youtube/ysc/) | session | Store and track interaction |
| [PREF](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/youtube/pref/) | 8 months | Store user preferences |

| Functional |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [VISITOR\_INFO1\_LIVE](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/youtube/visitor_info1_live/) | 6 months | Provide bandwidth estimations |

#### Facebook

##### Usage

We use Facebook for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons. [Read more](https://cookiedatabase.org/service/facebook/)

##### Sharing data

For more information, please read the [Facebook Privacy Statement](https://www.facebook.com/policy/cookies).

| Marketing/Tracking |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [\_fbc](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/facebook/_fbc/) | 2 years | Store last visit |
| [fbm\*](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/facebook/fbm_/) | 1 year | Store account details |
| [xs](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/facebook/xs/) | 3 months | Store a unique session ID |
| [fr](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/facebook/fr/) | 3 months | Provide ad delivery or retargeting |
| [act](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/facebook/act/) | 90 days | Store logged in users |
| [\_fbp](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/facebook/_fbp/) | 3 months | Store and track visits across websites |
| [datr](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/facebook/datr/) | 2 years | Provide fraud prevention |
| [c\_user](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/facebook/c_user/) | 30 days | Store a unique user ID |
| [sb](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/facebook/sb/) | 2 years | Store browser details |
| [\*\_fbm\_](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/facebook/_fbm_/) | 1 year | Store account details |

| Functional |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [wd](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/facebook/wd/) | 1 week | Read screen resolution |
| [csm](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/facebook/csm/) | 90 days | Provide fraud prevention |
| [actppresence](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/facebook/actppresence/) | session | Store and track if the browser tab is active |

#### LinkedIn

##### Usage

We use LinkedIn for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons. [Read more](https://cookiedatabase.org/service/linkedin/)

##### Sharing data

For more information, please read the [LinkedIn Privacy Statement](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy).

| Marketing/Tracking |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [bcookie](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/linkedin/bcookie-2/) | 2 years | Store browser details |
| [li-oatml](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/linkedin/li-oatml/) | 1 month | Provide ad delivery or retargeting |
| [li\_sugr](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/linkedin/li_sugr/) | 3 months | Store browser details |
| [UserMatchHistory](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/linkedin/usermatchhistory/) | 30 days | Provide ad delivery or retargeting |
| [lidc](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/linkedin/lidc/) | 1 day | Store performed actions on the website |
| [bscookie](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/linkedin/bscookie/) | 2 years | Store performed actions on the website |
| [X-LI-IDC](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/linkedin/x-li-idc/) | session | Provide functions across pages |

| Functional |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [BizographicsOptOut](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/linkedin/bizographicsoptout/) | 10 years | Store privacy preferences |
| [linkedin\_oauth\_](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/linkedin/linkedin_oauth_/) | session | Provide functions across pages |

#### Instagram

##### Usage

We use Instagram for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons. [Read more](https://cookiedatabase.org/service/instagram/)

##### Sharing data

For more information, please read the [Instagram Privacy Statement](https://privacycenter.instagram.com/policy/).

| Marketing/Tracking |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [actppresence](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/instagram/actppresence-2/) | 1 year | Store ad display frequency |

#### TikTok

##### Usage

We use TikTok for video display. [Read more](https://cookiedatabase.org/service/tiktok/)

##### Sharing data

For more information, please read the [TikTok Privacy Statement](https://www.tiktok.com/legal/privacy-policy).

| Marketing/Tracking |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [s\_v\_web\_id](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/tiktok/s_v_web_id/) | session | Store if the user has seen embedded content |
| [MONITOR\_WEB\_ID](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/tiktok/auto-draft-10/) | 3 months | Store if the user has seen embedded content |
| [tt\_webid](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/tiktok/tt_webid/) | 1 year | Store if the user has seen embedded content |
| [tt\_webid\_v2](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/tiktok/tt_webid_v2/) | 1 year | Store if the user has seen embedded content |
| [ttwid](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/tiktok/ttwid/) | 1 year | Store if the user has seen embedded content |
| [webapp\_launch\_mode](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/tiktok/webapp_launch_mode/) | session | Store if the user has seen embedded content |
| [webapp\_session\_id](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/tiktok/webapp_session_id/) | session | Store a unique session ID |
| [webapp-session-referer](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/tiktok/webapp-session-referer/) | session | Store referring website |
| [webapp\_tiktok\_privious](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/tiktok/webapp_tiktok_privious/) | session | Store if the user has seen embedded content |
| [webapp\_extra\_data](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/tiktok/webapp_extra_data/) | session | Provide functions across pages |
| [webapp\_original\_traffic\_type](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/tiktok/auto-draft-7/) | session | Store if the user has seen embedded content |
| [guide-login-config](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/tiktok/guide-login-config/) | persistent | Store a unique user ID |
| [\_\_tea\_cache\_tokens\_\*](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/tiktok/__tea_cache_tokens_/) | persistent | Store a unique session ID |

| Functional |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [csrf\_session\_id](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/tiktok/csrf_session_id/) | session | Provide protection against hackers |
| [tt\_csrf\_token](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/tiktok/auto-draft-9/) | session | Provide protection against hackers |
| [\_abck](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/tiktok/_abck/) | 1 year | Provide protection against hackers |
| [webapp-newuser](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/tiktok/webapp-newuser/) | persistent | Store first visit to the site |
| [autoplay-config](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/tiktok/autoplay-config/) | persistent | Store configuration |
| [webapp-video-mute](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/tiktok/webapp-video-mute/) | persistent | Store configuration |

| Purpose pending investigation |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [\_\_tea\_cache\_first\_\*](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/tiktok/__tea_cache_first_/) | persistent |     |
| [f](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/tiktok/f/) | persistent |     |

#### WP Engine

##### Usage

We use WP Engine for website hosting. [Read more](https://cookiedatabase.org/service/wp-engine/)

##### Sharing data

For more information, please read the [WP Engine Privacy Statement](https://wpengine.com/legal/privacy/).

| Purpose pending investigation |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| [rtk\_gdpr\_c](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/wp-engine/rtk_gdpr_c/) | session |     |
| [rtkuuid](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/wp-engine/rtkuuid/) | session |     |
| [rtk\_gdpr\_a](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/wp-engine/rtk_gdpr_a/) | session |     |
| [rtk\_p](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/wp-engine/rtk_p/) | session |     |
| [rtk\_sid](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/wp-engine/rtk_sid/) | session |     |
| [rtk\_rps](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/wp-engine/rtk_rps/) | session |     |
| [rtk\_sat](https://cookiedatabase.org/cookie/wp-engine/rtk_sat/) | session |     |

#### Miscellaneous

##### Sharing data

Sharing of data is pending investigation

| Purpose pending investigation |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name | Expiration | Function |
| rs-addon-notice |     |     |
| WP\_DATA\_USER\_66 |     |     |
| ate\_widget\_fetch\_time |     |     |
| continueReview |     |     |
| e\_kit-elements-defaults |     |     |
| WP\_DATA\_USER\_65 |     |     |
| ate\_widget\_url |     |     |
| loglevel |     |     |
| ezTOC\_hidetoc-0 |     |     |
| hubspotutk |     |     |
| debug |     |     |
| cmplz\_cookie\_data | 365 days |     |
| is\_eu |     |     |
| \_gcl\_au |     |     |
| \_\_hssrc |     |     |
| cmplz\_policy\_id | 365 days |     |
| \_gd\_svisitor |     |     |
| \_gd\_visitor |     |     |
| cmplz\_consented\_services | 365 days |     |
| cmplz\_marketing | 365 days |     |
| cmplz\_statistics | 365 days |     |
| cmplz\_preferences | 365 days |     |
| cmplz\_functional | 365 days |     |
| cmplz\_banner-status | 365 days |     |
| outbrain\_cid\_fetch |     |     |
| \_gid |     |     |
| ln\_or |     |     |
| \_hjIncludedInSessionSample\_2828349 |     |     |
| \_hjSession\_2828349 |     |     |
| \_hjAbsoluteSessionInProgress |     |     |
| \_gd\_session |     |     |
| \_an\_uid |     |     |
| wordpress\_test\_cookie |     |     |
| \_gat\_UA-56661828-1 |     |     |
| \_derived\_epik |     |     |
| \_ga\_B93FPS332E |     |     |
| \_cfuvid |     |     |
| \_pin\_unauth\_ls |     |     |
| \_derived\_epik\_ls |     |     |
| wp-autosave-1 |     |     |
| \_hjFirstSeen |     |     |
| acf |     |     |
| \_pin\_unauth\_ls |     |     |
| \_derived\_epik\_ls |     |     |
| wp-autosave-1 |     |     |
| \_hjFirstSeen |     |     |
| li\_fat\_id |     |     |
| wp\_lang |     |     |
| hjViewportId |     |     |
| \_hjRecordingLastActivity |     |     |
| \_hjRecordingEnabled |     |     |
| omWpApi |     |     |
| \_hjIncludedInSessionSample\_3485047 |     |     |
| \_hjSession\_3485047 |     |     |
| \_ga\_MS42QE6F0Z |     |     |
| \_gcl\_aw |     |     |
| \_gac\_UA-56661828-1 |     |     |
| WP\_PREFERENCES\_USER\_66 |     |     |
| \_gat\_gtag\_UA\_126880561\_2 |     |     |
| \_vwo\_uuid\_v2 |     |     |
| \_ga\_L6QC0Z83NG |     |     |
| cmplz\_consenttype | 365 days |     |
| 365 days |     |     |
| vwoSn |     |     |
| \_seg\_uid\_15103 |     |     |
| \_seg\_uid |     |     |
| \_seg\_visitor\_15103 |     |     |
| \_vwo\_uuid |     |     |
| \_vwo\_ds |     |     |
| \_vis\_opt\_s |     |     |
| \_vis\_opt\_test\_cookie |     |     |
| \_vis\_opt\_exp\_1\_combi |     |     |
| \_vis\_opt\_exp\_1\_goal\_1 |     |     |
| \_vis\_opt\_exp\_2\_combi |     |     |
| \_vis\_opt\_exp\_3\_combi |     |     |
| \_vis\_opt\_exp\_2\_goal\_1 |     |     |
| \_vis\_opt\_exp\_2\_goal\_2 |     |     |
| \_vis\_opt\_exp\_2\_goal\_3 |     |     |
| \_vis\_opt\_exp\_2\_goal\_4 |     |     |
| \_\_anon\_id |     |     |
| \_vwo\_sn |     |     |
| hjActiveViewportIds |     |     |
| \_\_mpq\_a36067b00a263cce0299cfd960e26ecf\_ev |     |     |
| mp\_a36067b00a263cce0299cfd960e26ecf\_mixpanel |     |     |
| \_mkto\_trk |     |     |
| \_zitok |     |     |
| lastExternalReferrer |     |     |
| lastExternalReferrerTime |     |     |
| dicbo\_fetch |     |     |
| redux\_current\_tab\_get |     |     |
| redux\_current\_tab |     |     |
| nectar\_wpbakery\_settings\_pos |     |     |
| WP\_PREFERENCES\_USER\_83 |     |     |
| \_vis\_opt\_exp\_3\_goal\_1 |     |     |
| \_\_cf\_bm |     |     |
| dicbo\_id |     |     |
| \_vwo |     |     |
| \_ga\_6FM2VVQSW2 |     |     |

### 7\. Consent

When you visit our website for the first time, we will show you a Cookie Banner with an explanation about cookies. As soon as you click on “Save preferences", you consent to us using the categories of cookies and plug-ins you selected in the Cookie Banner, and in accordance with this Cookie Policy. You can disable the use of cookies via your browser, but please note that our website may no longer work properly.

#### 7.1 Manage your consent settings

##### Functional (Always active)

Our functional cookies are always active as they are necessary for the functioning of our website. They are usually only set in response to actions made by you, which amount to a request for services, such as setting your privacy preferences, logging in to our platform, or filling in forms. You may block these cookies using your browser settings, but without these cookies our site may not function properly.

##### Preferences

These cookies allow us to remember information that changes the way that our website behaves or looks, like your preferred language.

##### Statistics

These cookies collect information about how you use our website, including which pages you visited and which links you clicked on. This allows us to understand how visitors interact with our website.

##### Marketing

We work with third parties who use cookies and similar technologies to collect information about the pages, links, and other websites you visit. These cookies are also used to deliver advertisements that are more relevant to you and your interests when you are on other websites across the internet. The information collected by these cookies will be used to track visits and actions on our platform, as well as to deliver reporting and analytics to us and our partners.

### 8\. Enabling/disabling and deleting cookies

You can block cookies through the mechanisms described below. However, note that cookies are important to many aspects of our website. If you disable all cookies or do not consent to our use of cookies when presented with our Cookie Banner, you may not be able to enjoy all the features we offer.

* **Revoke consent:** You may revoke your consent at any time with future effect by changing your cookie settings via our Cookie Banner.
    
* **Blocking Cookies in your browser.** Most browsers let you remove or reject cookies, including cookies used for interest-based advertising. To do this, follow the instructions in your browser settings. Many browsers accept cookies by default until you change your settings. For more information about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set on your device and how to manage and delete them, visit [allaboutcookies.org](https://allaboutcookies.org/). Use the following links to learn more about how to control Cookies and online tracking through your browser:
    
    * [Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/cookies-information-websites-store-on-your-computer); [Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?co=GENIE.Platform=Desktop&hl=en); [Microsoft Edge](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/windows/delete-and-manage-cookies-168dab11-0753-043d-7c16-ede5947fc64d); [Safari](https://support.apple.com/en-gb/guide/safari/sfri11471/mac)
        
* **Blocking advertising ID use in your mobile settings.** Your mobile device settings may provide functionality to limit use of the advertising ID associated with your mobile device for interest-based advertising purposes.
    
* **Using privacy plug-ins or browsers.** You can block our Service from setting cookies used for interest-based ads by using a browser with privacy features, like Brave, or installing browser plugins like [Privacy Badger](https://privacybadger.org/), [DuckDuckGo](https://duckduckgo.com/app), [Ghostery](https://www.ghostery.com/) or [uBlock Origin](https://ublockorigin.com/), and configuring them to block third-party cookies and trackers.
    
* **Advertising industry opt-out tools.** You can also use these opt-out options to limit the use of your information for interest-based advertising by participating companies:

* **Platform opt-outs.** The following advertising partners offer opt-out features that let you opt out of the use of your information for interest-based advertising:

Note that the above opt-out mechanisms are specific to the device or browser on which they are exercised. You will need to opt out on every browser and device that you use.

If you do delete the cookies in your browser, we will ask to place them, with your consent, when you visit our websites again.

### 9\. Changes to our Cookie Policy

We keep our Cookie Policy under regular review, and we will place any updates on this web page. We will indicate at the top of this page when the policy was most recently updated.

### 10\. Contact details

For questions and/or comments about our Cookie Policy and this statement, please contact us by using the following contact details:

Mavrck LLC  
53 State Street  
21st Floor – Suite 2105  
Boston, MA 02109  
United States  
Website: app.mavrck.co  
Email: [privacy@mavrck.co](mailto:privacy@mavrck.co)  
Phone number: 1-844-MAVRCK1

The best social media marketing app, influencer marketing management platform & Link in Bio tool.

    Later Social submenu
    
    Platforms

    Solutions

    Instagram Features

    Later Users

    Pricing

    Later Influence submenu
    
    Solutions

    Tools

    Influencers

    Services

    Use Cases

    Demo

    Link in Bio submenu
    
    Solutions

* Company

* Resources

Download

Follow Us

Join Our Newsletter

Partnerships

* © 2024 Later. All Rights Reserved.
    
* Cookie Settings
